JOON YOUNG JEONG

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



NZ Permernent Resident



(<u>∞</u>) <u>juny.jeong@gmail.com</u>



n <u>Linkedin Profile</u>



<u>Github</u>



<u>Portfolio</u>

ABOUT ME

My passion for tech started in the 1990s, when I learned visual basic. Although I have worked in other industries since then, this passion has always been with me. As a highly selfmotivated indivdual, I decided to return to where my true passion is with valuable skills and experiences acquired along the way.

SKILLS

TECH

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Express, Node.js, Knex, Sqlite3, Git, JEST. Acquired and practiced during the courses of Dev Academy.

PROBLEM SOLVING

As a student at Dev Academy and in my previous role as Accounting Manager, I consistently faced unforeseen challenges and took pleasure in successfully resolving them

TEAM WORK

Developed skills while working within a team and with various people during my time at Dev Academy and also in my previous role as Accounting Manager. Quickly adapt to a team environment and contribute a can-do attitude to achieve a team goal.

OUICK LEARNER

Came to NZ in 2005 and finished my BA 4 years later. For tech, Starting from zero to Full Stack Developer in 17 weeks of boot camp. Those achievements will explain the skill.

TIME MANAGEMENT

In my previous role as Accounting Manager, I successfully managed to prepare for tax, financial information for annual report with tight deadlines. I also manged to complete various weekly challenges and projects during the course at Dev Academy.

page continues

EXPERIENCE

STUDENT - FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Dev Academy Aotearoa

JAN 2023 - MAY 2023

- 17 weeks immersive full-time software development boot camp. Throughout the course, I was involved in various weekly projects and challenges using full-stack software development tools.
- Most of the challenges and projects were completed as pair programming or as a group. While completing those projects and challenges within a given time in a team environment I was able to build and practice soft skills.
- Skill Acquired: feedback, listening and looping, agile planning, time management

ACCOUNTING MANAGER

Oriana Enterprises Ltd

JUN 2015 - DEC 2022

- During this time I was responsible for overseeing a company's financial activities and acting as liaison with an external accountant.
- Skill acquired: communication
- Had to prepare for tax and various reports with tight deadlines.
- Skill acquired: time management
- Interacted with people of different part of company, (eg, inventory, sales etc) and had to oversee company's operation to ensure it was optimized to track and record financial activity. Implement new process or adjust existing process when it was required.
- Skill acquired: team work, problem solving

EDUCATION

NZQA LEVEL 6, CERTIFICATE OF APPLIED SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

DEV ACADEMY AOTEAROA | AUCKLAND JAN 2023 - MAY 2023

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE,
ACCOUNTING & INFOMATION SYSTEM

UNIVERSITY OF AUCKLAND | AUCKLAND MAR 2007 - SEP 2010

REFERENCE

Available on request.